Four.
- Next.
- Four. Two.
- Yes!
- Five.
- Nice. I got three.
- Five? Why?
- Four.
- Nice!
- Four?
- Four.
Darn it!
Two. Three.
Three. One.
I can't hear you.
(The following graph shows...)
(Park Ji Hoon)
(Choi Hyun Wook)
(Hong Kyung)
(Lee Yeon)
(Shin Seung Ho)
(Weak Hero Class 1)
(Screenplay and production by Yu Su Min)
(Originated from "Weak Hero"
by Seo Pae Seu and Kim Jin Seok)
(Byeoksan High School
Seoul National University: 3 admitted)
("The bird fights its way
out of the egg.")
(From "Demian" by Hermann Hesse)
(13 days earlier)
Quadratic formula.
Write the unknowns
and the constants on the left...
in descending order...
and set the equation equal to zero...
so it's "ax" squared plus
"by" squared plus "c..."
equals zero.
Well done, Si Eun.
(1. English: Reading comprehension,
2. Math: 2021 mock test)
The Imo Incident. In 1882, during
the 19th year of King Gojong's reign,
the discrimination...
against the soldiers
of the traditional army...
and Joseon's military reform...
had sparked an uprising.
Which resulted
in the Heungseon Daewongun's return...
to power and...
Active voice.
The object of Pattern four active is
the subject of a passive.
A pattern 4 sentence has 2 objects,
so it can be converted to two passives
where each of them are subjects.
(13 days until the mock test)
Two people in this class won awards
in our school's math competition.
Yeon Si Eun, Jeon Yeong Bin,
come to the front.
Yes!
"First place winner, Yeon Si Eun."
"This award is presented
to this student..."
"in recognition of their achievement
in this math competition."
Good job.
"Third place winner, Jeon Yeong Bin."
The same as above.
A round of applause!
So the mock test
is in less than two weeks.
Are you all working hard for it?
- Yes, ma'am.
If you don't work hard,
you may regret it later
when you take the actual exam.
- It's got to be sexier.
- Move your hips.
Nice. Keep going.
Come on. Move your hips.
- There you go!
- Nice.
Sexier.
Turn around, you prick.
What a moron.
Hey, you know
people love your videos, right?
Soon, you're going to rise to fame.
Think about it. You don't study,
you've got no connections,
and you've got no money.
This is your best chance to make money.
You should be thankful.
I know. I am thankful.
Then get me some Gatorade.
- I want Milkis.
- Coke Zero for me.
I guess that didn't hurt so much.
He needs a good beating.
I know, right?
Hey.
Give it to me.
What's up?
Hey, you've got to aim better.
You just hit this boy.
He's right. Come on.
Right. I'm sorry. Get back to studying.
Sorry.
Be careful next time.
It was an accident.
What's there to be careful about?
You're just trying to show me up.
I know it was an accident.
So be careful not to cause another one.
What the...
Hey.
You know what?
People hate you.
Whatever you say, it sounds annoying.
What do you think?
Are you bored?
What?
Why don't you stop wasting your time
and go study English?
Do you have a death wish?
Who is An Soo Ho?
Soo Ho. An Soo Ho.
What? Is it lunchtime already?
Are you An Soo Ho?
You hit on Na Eun, didn't you?
Na Eun?
Lee Na Eun?
Park Na Eun?
It's Son Na Eun, you jerk!
Oh, her. She kept messaging me,
so I had a meal with her once.
I'm not interested in her.
She's not my type.
- Hey, what's today's lunch menu?
- Stir-fried pork.
Oh, that's great. I like protein.
Guys.
Hey, stop.
Got you.
Hey, come here.
Are you sure you're in a sports club?
You!
- You're going to leave now?
- Okay, darn it!
You jerk!
You crossed the line.
Whatever, you darn punk!
Take him to the nurse's office.
Don't say my name, or I'll kill you.
But we're older than him.
Let's go.
Oh, was that me?
Yes.
Sorry, man.
Why would you do that in the classroom?
(Math Competition Award, Yeon Si Eun)
What's the point
of all the sports massages?
Koreans need to eat rice to stay strong.
Yes.
And if you sneak out again,
I'm going to kill you.
All right. See you later.
Hi, Son. You're back.
I'm afraid I need to go
to another training camp.
I won't be back for the next two weeks.
Call me if you need me.
Okay.
Your teacher has called.
She said you won first place
at the math competition.
"First place winner, Yeon Si Eun."
You make me so proud, Si Eun.
Thank you, Son.
Sure.
Hey. What's up?
What are you talking about?
I talked to them already.
So that's what this is about.
Do you understand?
All right. So draw each graph...
to find the points of intersection.
Do you keep in touch?
I'm just studying.
I'm leaving now.
- Have a safe trip.
- Thanks.
Do you understand?
You see, my son is
the top student at school.
But I never nag him.
Do you know why?
Because he does well on his own.
As I always say, studying is...
(Byeoksan High School)
What...
This is amazing.
- She's so hot.
- Do you want me to set you up with her?
- Yes!
- Let me see.
So sexy. She's my type.
Why him?
Well, shut it.
Look at your face, moron.
Look at your body, moron.
- You call that a muscle?
- What do you think it is then?
Stop. I'll introduce her to both of you.
Hey, brush your teeth.
- Just shut it.
- I'll let you have her.
Hey, what do you think of mine?
I bet it's tiny.
Whose is bigger?
What are you looking at?
What's the matter? Did you lose something?
I could just fold you in half.
Let's go.
I have muscles.
You call them biceps?
What else are they then? Monoceps?
You moron. Why would you say that?
Come on! Let's go!
That was 6 minutes and 12 seconds.
Take 5 seconds off.
Soo Ho, why don't you study
sports in college?
You're more than qualified for it.
Well, it's not like I'm going to be
a national player.
I'll think about it
when I break Bolt's record.
Bolt? Bolt who?
You know, Usain Bolt.
- Thanks for the class, sir.
- That punk.
- That was 6 minutes and 45 seconds.
- What?
Don't walk. Keep running!
My legs hurt. It's killing me!
You're almost there! Keep it up!
Look at that idiot running.
Is he a zombie or what?
He might as well run like this.
Oh, come on.
"You jerks."
"Wait there, you jerks."
Bring it to me.
Ignore him.
He's right. Just ignore him.
What was your name again?
I'm Lee Jeong Chan.
Okay.
Well done.
That was 9 minutes and 48 seconds.
Yeon Si Eun, you've got to work
on your stamina.
You need to stay healthy
to study, you know.
Boys, take him to the nurse's office.
No, I'm okay, sir.
I'm okay.
"I'm okay."
Of course he's not okay.
He didn't sound okay.
Seriously, Yeong Bin.
We've got to beat him up once.
Remember his eyes?
"Be careful next time."
"Be careful
not to cause another accident."
Those darn eyes.
Give me some.
I smell something stinky.
Jeez, he reeks of sweat.
I want to throw up.
Stop this. I'm asking you.
What?
Stop bothering me.
I'm not sure what you're talking about.
This is a warning.
See? He's acting cool and all,
but he's just a loser.
Let go.
That's not how you ask someone a favor.
Now try again.
What?
What if he actually dies?
Maybe we should call a teacher.
Yeong Bin.
Don't let him go, or I'll kill you.
Hey! What are you doing over there?
Nothing. We were just messing around.
Si Eun, are you okay?
- Han Tae Hoon.
- Yes?
What's going on?
- Hey.
- We were just messing around, sir.
You don't want trouble, do you?
You need to go to college.
Yeon Si Eun, you tell me.
Were you really just messing around?
Yes, sir. We were just messing around.
- Don't do it again, okay?
- Yes, sir.
What are those merchants called?
Gongin.
Gongin is very important.
So when you see
this law in the question...
When there's gongin, find the Daedong Law.
Then this currency started to circulate...
Who is it?
Delivery.
I didn't order food.
What? But this is the address.
Hey, bookworm. What are you doing here?
I didn't order food.
Isn't this Unit 902
of Dongbaek Apartment's Building 102?
This is Building 101.
It says it's Building 102.
Oh, well.
Hey, buddy. Can I have a glass of water?
- Why should I?
- Come on. We're classmates.
- Don't be like that.
- What?
It's just a glass of water.
What if I pass out from dehydration?
It's your fault then.
Seriously, it's just a glass of water.
Don't just stand there.
I'm about to pass out.
My voice is getting hoarse too.
Seriously, what's your problem?
Thanks, man. I'll get you
three bottles of water tomorrow.
Keep up with your study,
and see you tomorrow.
And be good to your mom.
We have a new student.
Bum Seok, say hi to your new classmates.
Hi, I'm Oh Bum Seok.
Be nice to Bum Seok, okay?
Hey, let's go.
Hi.
- Oh Bum Seok, was it?
- Yes.
Where did you come from?
I transferred from Mungang High School.
His family must be rich.
If you're from Mungang,
you must know Ji Won.
We're best friends.
I'm afraid I don't know who that is.
You don't know Han Ji Won?
The name sounds familiar,
but I don't know.
Move.
That's my seat.
I don't want to.
I said, move.
Have you lost your mind?
Why are you guys so chatty these days?
Someone's trying to sleep here.
Can I sleep in peace? Please?
You better be careful.
- Cheers!
Yeong Bin, are you sure
you don't want to drink?
He's right. Why won't you drink?
The mock test's next week, you morons.
Study hard and get a job in a big company.
By the way, I think
Yeon Si Eun is losing his mind.
Who does he think he is?
As if he could actually
do something with that pen.
I saw him look at us the other day,
and he looked crazy.
I almost killed him.
Oh, come on. You didn't do anything.
Seriously,
I just wanted to break his neck.
What should we do with Yeon Si Eun?
We just can't seem to hurt him.
We can't hurt his soul.
Maybe his grades.
I mean, he's obsessed with his grades.
Maybe if we mess with that,
it'll destroy his soul.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
You idiot. As if you will get it.
What's the narrator feeling here?
What do you think?
The answer is anxiety.
Anxiety.
"Even a rustling leaf comes to me."
- Oh, hey. You're here.
- Hello.
- He actually brought it.
- No way.
It's from Cheonan.
And 100 dollars for the distance.
Finally, the fentanyl's here.
Hey, you should pay.
You're the only one who hasn't paid yet.
Give him 100 dollars.
Are you sure that's enough?
Here. It's for you.
Hey, count it.
I trust you.
Wait. I'll come with you.
I need to ask you something.
- Hey, where are you going?
- I'm taking a private lesson.
Bye.
- Have fun.
- Thank you.
- Are you really leaving?
- Bye.
- Why does he study so hard?
- See you!
He's always like that.
- Darn it.
- Did he really leave?
Hey.
Auntie came over the other day.
She said you hadn't come home yet.
Get to the point.
I just wonder...
What happens
if you put fentanyl on your skin?
On your neck, for example?
It won't be as potent,
but it's still a painkiller.
It'll make you feel a little muzzy.
You'll get dull and sleepy.
In the worse case, you'll vomit.
Why do you ask?
Oh, I just got curious.
- Yeong Bin.
- Yes?
Don't go overboard.
What are you talking about?
Bye.
What a jerk.
Hi, Ji Won. How have you been?
(Father: Is everything all right?)
(Yes)
Are you...
Normally, we just drop it off, you know.
This is the last time
we deliver it to you.
Come on.
Hey, I said it's a girl.
Darn. We messed up.
Move.
What?
Move. You're standing in my way.
Well, I don't like that tone.
You must have a death wish.
I don't like those eyes either.
Hey, quit staring.
Or I'm going to smash your stupid head.
Hey.
Leave.
Know who you're messing with.
He was about to attack you.
(1 day until the mock test)
Hey.
Bum Seok, our teacher wants to see you.
- What?
- Our homeroom teacher wants to see you.
Drink this.
Thanks.
By the way, it seemed like
you had some hard time in Mungang.
I talked to Ji Won yesterday.
What?
He said you were beaten and bullied there.
Nice one!
Is that why you transferred here?
Like a loser?
Well...
I'm not trying to scare you or anything.
I hope we can be friends.
Take a seat.
Okay.
Aren't you thankful?
I'm keeping your secret
and asking you to be friends.
Yes. Thank you.
Then could you do me a favor?
What's this?
Take it.
You know Korean exams
can take quite some time, right?
- Yes, ma'am.
Distribute your time well.
And no cheating.
- Yes, ma'am.
There was a fly.
Hey, what are you doing?
Turn around.
It won't be as potent,
but it's still a painkiller.
It'll make you feel a little muzzy.
You'll get dull and sleepy.
In the worse case, you'll vomit.
In literature,
objects can be represented...
by other related objects or ideas.
For instance, the attribute of an object
can represent the object itself...
or a part of it can represent the whole.
These media can be mixed...
Hey. Where are you going?
What was that?
What are you doing? What's wrong?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
- The questions were...
- Two.
- Nice.
- Five.
- How many?
- Three.
Five. Next, social studies.
One. One.
Five. Four.
Five. Five.
Four. Two.
- Darn it.
- Two?
Five. Four.
Three. One.
Four.
- It was confusing.
- He's better than me.
- This one is...
- Hey.
Si Eun. It's not what you think.
Newton's second law.
The force is proportional
to the mass and acceleration.
Using the centrifugal force,
one can create a greater impact.
What a nut!
Wait.
I asked you.
I asked you to stop.
Enough. Don't cross the line.
Who do you think you are?
Me? A guardian angel
who just woke up from a nap.
You think this is funny?
It's supposed to be funny.
(All firms, characters, locations, names,
and events in this work are fictitious.)
(Any resemblance to actual events
or persons is purely coincidental.)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)